Guide to the Warwick Baker O'Neill Records, 1931-2001 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1985-1998 and undated
  - Crafted with Pride--Crate/Line. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV2)
  - Crafted with Pride--DuPont Talking Shirt. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV2)
  - Crafted with Pride--Excuses. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV2)
  - Crafted with Pride--Excuses. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV2)
  - Crafted with Pride--Feet Keep America Moving. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 13:34 (Box AV2)
  - Crafted with Pride--Historical. 1994. Umatic. TRT: 6:30 (Box AV2)
  - Crafted with Pride--Historical. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV2)
  - Crafted with Pride--Industry spots. 1994. Umatic. TRT: 7:20 (Box AV2)
  - Crafted with Pride--It Matters Tell All the World. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV2)
  - Crafted with Pride--Leonard Horn/Miss America interview. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV2)
  - Crafted with Pride--Line/Crate. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Made in the USA/Miss America. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miscellaneous clips. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America Bumpers. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America client interview. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America farewell speech.1989. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America Pageant part 1. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 60:00 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America Pageant. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America Pageant. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America Pageant. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America Pageant. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America news clips. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America non-finalist talent winners. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV3)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America promotion. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 2:36 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America sponsorship. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--Miss America rehearsals, interviews. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--News clips. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--NFA Bobbin Show. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--Pride. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 1:10 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--Pride. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 1:10 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--Pride Belk/Gastner/Gottschalk's. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 1:15 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--Pride G. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--Pride Jones Store/Belk Simpson/Thalhimer's. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--Pride Lion/Gastner Knott. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--Quick Changes. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--Quick Changes. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--Research, Visa/Barbara Mandrell. 1994. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--Research, Visa/Barbara Mandrell. 1994. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV4)
  - Crafted with Pride--Sally Struthers/Quick Changes. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV5)
  - Crafted with Pride--Tell All the World/Sally Struthers/Quick Changes. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV5)
  - Crafted with Pride--Tell All the World/Sally Struthers/Quick Changes. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV5)
  - Crafted with Pride--Video Newsletter. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 27:00 (Box AV5)
  - Crafted with Pride--Update. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV5)
  - Crafted with Pride--Warwick Advertising special presentation. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV5)
  - Crafted with Pride--What a Feeling/Filene's. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV5)
  - Crafted with Pride--What a Feeling Jacket Label. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 0:45 (Box AV5)
  - Crafted with Pride--What a Feeling Jacket Label. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 0:45 (Box AV5)
  - Crafted with Pride--What a Feeling/Moving/Excuses. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV5)
  - Crafted with Pride--What a Feeling Jacket Label. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV5)
  - Crafted with Pride--What a Feeling Jacket Label. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 0:45 (Box AV5)
  - Crafted with Pride--What a Feeling Jacket Label. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 2:30 (Box AV5)
  - Crafted with Pride--What a Feeling Joslin's/Jones Store. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV5)
  - Crafted with Pride--What a Feeling NFA. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box AV5)
  - Donow & Associates--Consumers. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV6)
  - Donow & Associates--Consumers. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV6)
  - Donow & Associates--Consumers. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV6)
  - Donow & Associates--Consumers. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV6)
  - Donow & Associates--MFS Brokers. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV6)
  - Donow & Associates--MFS Brokers. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV6)
  - Donow & Associates--Non MFS Brokers. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV6)
  - Donow & Associates--Non MFS Brokers. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV6)
  - Donow & Associates--Non MFS Brokers. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV6)
  - Donow & Associates--Non MFS Brokers. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV6)
  - Gleneagles focus group 1 tape 1. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV6)
  - Gleneagles focus group 1 tape 2. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV6)
  - Gleneagles focus group 1 tape 3. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV6)
  - Gleneagles focus group 2 tape 1. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV6)
  - Gleneagles focus group 2 tape 2. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV6)
  - Gleneagles focus group 2 tape 3. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV6)
  - Gleneagles focus group 2 tape 4. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV6)
  - Gleneagles No. 1. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV6)
  - Gleneagles No. 2. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV6)
  - Gleneagles No. 3. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV6)
  - Gleneagles No. 4. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV6)
  - Golfers tape 1. 1997. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV6)
  - Golfers tape 2.1997. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV6)
  - Golfers tape 3. 1997. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV6)
  - Golfing Apparel and Gleneagles. 1997. VHS. TRT: 19:00 (Box AV6)
  - Lea & Perrins Teriyaki, Worcester. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 0:45 (Box AV6)
  - MFS consumers. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - MFS focus groups. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV7)
  - MFS focus groups. Undated. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - MFS focus group no. 1. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - MFS focus group no. 2. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - MFS focus group no. 3. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - New/Used car focus group--New. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - New/Used car focus group--Used. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - New/Used car/truck/van one-on-one interviews tape 1. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - New/Used car/truck/van one-on-one interviews tape 2. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - Polly Graham--Group 1, females, non-buyers. 1997. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - Polly Graham--Group 2, females, buyers. 1997. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - Polly Graham--Group 3, males, non-buyers.1997. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - Polly Graham--Group 4, males, buyers.1997. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - RSI MPLS, new cars tape 1. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - RSI MPLS, new cars tape 2. 1996. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - Shaving--Chicago group 1. 1998. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - Shaving--Chicago group 2. 1998. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - Shaving--Chicago group 3. 1998. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - Shaving--Chicago group 4. 1998. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - Shaving--New Jersey group 1. Undated. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - Shaving--New Jersey group 2. Undated. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - Shaving--New Jersey group 3. Undated. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - Shaving--New Jersey group 4. Undated. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV7)
  - Television Register: Selected Buy Australian commercials. 1994. Umatic NTSC. TRT: 5:15 (Box AV7)
  - Used cars group 1A. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 60:00 (Box AV7)
  - Used cars group 1B. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 60:00 (Box AV7)
  - Used cars group 2A. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 60:00 (Box AV7)
  - Used cars group 2B. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 60:00 (Box AV7)
  - Amaretto College. 1998. Audiocassette. TRT: 90:00 (Box AV8)
  - B/R/S @ Focus Pointe. 1998. Audiocassette. TRT: 120:003 tapes. (Box AV8)
  - Buying patterns focus groups. 1994. Audiocassette. TRT: 120:008 tapes. (Box AV8)
  - Chicago focus groups. 1994. Audiocassette. TRT: 120:0011 tapes. (Box AV8)
  - Donow & Associates--Financial services study. 1996. Audiocassette. TRT: 120:005 tapes. (Box AV8)
  - Donow & Associates--MFS focus groups. 1996. Audiocassette. TRT: 120:0023 tapes. (Box AV8)
  - Golfers. 1997. Audiocassette. TRT: 120:003 tapes. (Box AV8)
  - Ladies' wear focus groups. 1997. Audiocassette. TRT: 120:004 tapes. (Box AV8)
  - Polly Graham--Group 1, females, non-buyers. 1997. Audiocassette. TRT: 120:002 tapes. (Box AV8)
  - Polly Graham--Group 2, females, buyers. 1997. Audiocassette. TRT: 120:002 tapes. (Box AV8)
  - Polly Graham--Group 3, males, non-buyers.1997. Audiocassette. TRT: 120:003 tapes. (Box AV8)
  - Polly Graham--Group 4, males, buyers.1997. Audiocassette. TRT: 120:002 tapes. (Box AV8)
  - Selfcare menopausal relief, soy supplement qualitative. Undated. Audiocassette. TRT: 120:00 (Box AV8)
  - WBO/Herron focus groups. 1997. Audiocassette. TRT: 120:006 tapes. (Box AV8)
  - Warwick Welsh & Miller: Red Rose--Torch, Slim King--Steam Room, Artra--Pool. Undated. 16mm. (Box AV9)
  - Brooke Bond Red Rose historical reel. Undated. 16mm. (Box AV9)